> > Brian Holt: 我还有一件事要给你看
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I got one more
thing I wanna show you here.
我想展示一下如何更新主题，对吗 ?
And I wanna show you how to
update the the theme, right?
到目前为止，我刚刚向大家展示了如何从主题中阅读，但是
So far, I've just shown you how
to read from the theme, but
我们还想更新主题
we also wanna be able to update the theme.
所以我想让你回到 SearchParams ，也就是 SearchParams。
So I want you to go back to
SearchParams as well, SearchParams.
我们要在 BreedDropdown 的下面制造另一个 Dropdown 。
We're going to make another Dropdown,
underneath BreedDropdown here.
我们会说标签 htmlFor= 位置。
We're gonna say label htmlFor= location.
>> Brian Holt: 对不起，不是位置，而是主题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Sorry,
not location but theme rather.
> > Brian Holt: 我们会有一个主题，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
we're gonna have a Theme there, and
我们要有个选择
we're gonna have a select.
这个价值将会是平等的主题。
And the value is going to equal theme.
而 onChange ，我们将设定主题，
And onChange,
we're going to set the theme,
因此， setTheme 为 ee.target.value，对于 onBlur相同。
so setTheme to be e.target.value,
and same thing for onBlur.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，让我们在此抓取 setTheme ，在顶部向上看，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's go grab
setTheme here, cuz up here at the top,
我们有主题但我们不是在抓 setTheme
we have theme, and
we're not grabbing setTheme.
所以我要用的是 setTheme ，以从 ThemeContext 中抓取。
So all I have to put here is setTheme
to grab that out of the ThemeContext.
再 Cuz ，这只是一个钩子，对吧 ?
Cuz again, this is just a hook, right?
这是一个正常的钩子，但是钩子会在应用程序中存在。
It's a normal hook, but
the hook lives in-app.
它并不是生活在 SearchParams中。
It doesn't actually live in SearchParams.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，然后我们在这里进行选择。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
then we have the select here.
> > Brian Holt: 接下来，我们将给出几个选项。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then here,
we're just gonna give a couple of options.
这里有我给的， peru，可爱的颜色，
So here's ones that I gave, peru,
cuz that's such a lovely color,
> > Brian Holt: 深蓝色，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: darkblue,
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 平庸
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: mediumorchid,
这颜色太好了
cuz that's a color.
>> Brian Holt: 还是另一个好的 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Or what's another good one?
我这里有什么
What do I have here?
很有魅力那是种颜色
chartreuse, that's a color.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，很多人可能想知道为什么我们不使用
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, a lot people will
probably wonder why don't we just use
又来了这看起来像个下拉的
Dropdown again,
this looks like a Dropdown.
我们不使用 Dropdown 的原因是 Dropdown 会产生它自己的钩子，对吗 ?
The reason why we're not using Dropdown is
cuz Dropdown creates its own hooks, right?
我们实际上是用别人的钩子
And we're actually using
someone else's hook.
我们正在使用应用程序挂钩，而不使用 SearchParams 挂钩。
We're using apps hooks,
we're not using SearchParams hooks.
所以我们不能用 Dropdown hook 的方式
So that's why we're not gonna
use our use Dropdown hook here.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，工作吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, is that working?
>> Brian Holt: 应该不错。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That should be good.
我们去看看它是否有效。
Let's go take a look and see if it works.
所以现在我有了一个新的 " Dropdown " 主题。
So now I have a new
Dropdown here with Theme.
如果我把它改为中等兰花对吧
If I change this to be Medium Orchid,
right,
那是一种漂亮的中奥兰花我猜是在查特鲁特还是秘鲁
that's a nice Medium Orchid I suppose,
or Chartreuse, or Peru.
但这里是有趣的部分。
But here is the interesting part of this.
如果这只是一个正常的钩子只要我浏览到细节页面
If this was just a normal hook, as soon
as I navigated to the details page,
我在解释这问题时把代码留在这里
I'll leave the code up here
while I'm explaining this.
只要我导航到细节页面就可以了，对吧 ?
As soon as I navigated to the details
page, right, it would drop that, right?
因为组件会被卸载，并且所有挂钩都将被销毁。
Because the component would get unmounted
and all of its hooks would be destroyed.
所以下次你回去的时候就会回到违约状态，对吧 ?
So it would go back to its default state
next time you went back to it, right?
同样地，
By the same token,
也不一定要更新细节页面，对吧 ?
it would not update necessarily
the details page either, right?
但因为现在这个生活在应用程序中，对，在应用程序中总是呈现的，对吗 ?
But because now this lives in-app, right,
and in-app is always rendered, right?
应用程序从不取消呈示。
In-app never unrenders.
因此，现在的优势在于状态将超越页面导航。
So the advantage of this is now the state
will live beyond page navigations.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 让我向你们展示一下我的观点，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let me demonstrate
my point to you here, right?
我们把它改为 " 中等兰花 " 对吧
Let's change this to be Medium Orchid,
right?
如果我到这里的详细信息页面， >> Brian Holt: 是蓝色的，为什么是蓝色的 ?
And if I go to the details page here,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's blue, why is it blue?
它应该留下
It should stay.
> > Brian Holt: 那不是应该发生的事情。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Well,
that's not what's supposed to happen.
这毁了我的意思
That ruins my point.
>> Brian Holt: SetTheme，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: SetTheme,
>> Brian Holt: 深蓝色， >> Brian Holt: 然后返回
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: darkblue,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then you go back to
主页。
the homepage.
>> Brian Holt: 秘鲁，然后浏览。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Peru, and then navigate.
它完全没有安装在页面上，这真的很有趣。
It's fully unmounting the page,
that's really interesting.
所以我不知道为什么它会完全卸载这个页面。
So I'm not sure why it's
fully unmounting the page.
我得去看看
I have to go look.
但你可以看到它实际上是在每次我浏览的时候清除控制台。
But you can see it's actually clearing the
console every single time that I navigate.
那就好
So that's fine.
>> Brian Holt: 此处的链接是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: What is the link there?
这是佩特的链接
That's the link coming from Pet.
这就是原因。
This is why.
我不知道我们为什么不去更新这个
I don't know why we didn't
ever end up updating this.
我们现在就进行更新。
Let's go ahead and update it now.
就在这里我们想进口林克
So here inside of pet.js
we want to import Link
从 @reach/router， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
from @reach/router,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
we're gonna change this a right
在这里， >> Brian Holt:
here,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Instead of being an a,
我们要把它连接起来
we're gonna make it a link.
而不是 href 而是我们要做的
Instead of an href,
we're gonna make this to.
>> Brian Holt:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right, and
我们只是把它从正常的主播标记改为链接标签
we just change this from being a normal
anchor tag to being a link tag.
而现在，在它实际上是在做一个完整的页面导航之前
And now, whereas before it was actually
doing a full page navigation was changing
页面，对吧 ?
the page, right?
所以它摧毁了这个领地，然后再次重建它。
So it was destroying the dom and
then rebuilding it again.
现在，它实际上是要用 HTML 历史来浏览这些页面。
Now, it's actually going to use
HTML history to navigate the pages.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，如果我把这个改变给兰花，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
now if I just change this to Orchid, and
然后我就去这里看胖子 Slim ，注意到它还是兰兰。
then I go to Fat Boy Slim here,
notice that it's still Orchid.
>> Brian Holt: 有道理吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Makes sense?
>> Brian Holt: 它是否也能检测到我的错误 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Did it also make
sense the error that I had?
很可能你看到了这个错误，因为你会看到这个错误。
It's probably good that you saw that error
because that's what you'll see if you
无意中忘记使用链接标记，而不使用标记。
accidentally forget to use a link tag,
instead of an a tag.
这是另一件事 [ INAUDIBLE ] 正在为你做。
It's another thing that
[INAUDIBLE] is doing for you.
>> 扬声器 2: 如果我们使用导航，那么此错误将不存在。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: This error wouldn't present
itself if we use the navigate though,
对吧 ?
right?
>> Brian Holt: 否，导航也会使用历史记录。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: No, yeah,
navigate would also use history as well.
这纯粹是你用的吧
This is purely if you use a, right?
因此，重定向将正确处理它，浏览将正常工作。
So redirect would handle it correctly,
navigate would work correctly.
只要你用一个就好了
It's just purely if you use a.
>> Brian Holt: 好的问题，其他问题?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Good question,
other questions?
>> 扬声器 3: 使用阵列破坏的挂钩种类，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: With the hooks kind of
utilizing the array destructuring,
如果你出于某种原因想退出政府
if you for some reason wanted
to pull out the updater, but
在某个地方不使用目前的国家，是否有这样做的惯例 ?
not use the current state somewhere,
is there a convention for doing that?
>> Brian Holt: 通常，您只会显示一个下划线，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Typically,
you just put an underscore,
埃斯皮林还是会对你大喊喊叫的
eslint is still gonna yell at you.
你把这条线禁用了对吧
And the way that you just
disable the line, right?
所以他在问我这里有什么挂钩
So what he's asking if I have a hook here,
let's just say const
blah equalah ， blah 和 setBlah，对，
blah equal, or blah and setBlah, right,
很明显是用了 lah 的国家
= useState with blah, obviously.
就像这样如果我不关心现在的情况
Like this, what happens if I don't
actually care what blah is right now,
我只是想更新一下
I just wanna update blah, right?
我要怎么做
How would I do that?
这就是我要做的事，我给自己下一个下划线
This is what I would do, I would put an
underscore there just to signify to myself
我没在用这一文不值
that I'm not using this,
this is worthless.
我也会用参数做同样的事
It's the same thing I'll
do with parameters as well.
>> Brian Holt: 但 eslint 会说这是未使用的变量，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But eslint is gonna
say this is unused variable and
我不喜欢这样，这样你就可以这样做了，就像是在说 " 不一样 " 的线。
I don't like that, so the way you can just
do that is just say eslint-disable line.
你可以告诉它禁止使用任何未使用的 vars
And you can actually tell it to
disable specifically no unused vars,
没有未使用的 vars，对吗 ?
no-unused-vars, right?
然后，它将专门针对该线路禁用该线路。
And then it will specifically
disable that for that line.
[ 空白音频]
[BLANK AUDIO]